The regenerative movement inspired by the developmental movement of the embryo. Initial position.
Push the right hand into the left hand, feet parallel.
Shoulder width apart.
The back is straight and relaxed.
Slight knee flexion.
And observation of the different median lines. The median line,
notochordal, posterior and anterior.
We clearly observe the neuro-sensory, rhythmic, metabolic, urogenital spheres.
Try to feel them, to balance yourself.
Initially, the ovular movement is spherical.
You draw a sphere in space in front of you that represents the ovum.
The primary function of the ovum in creation is primitive polarization.
An east-west axis.
And a north-south axis. North-south.
And front and back.
Arrival of the spermatozoon.
Penetration of the spermatozoon into the ovum.
And the first cleavage appears. You draw the first two blastomeres in space in front of you.
You can take the whole, cell division.
And you place this sphere downwards at the level of the abdomen.
Initially, no growth, but cell multiplication.
Then, the 4th movement is hatching.
Followed by nidation, appearance of the amniotic cavity,
and the external coelom, growth.
Formation of the embryonic pedicle. Establishment of the primitive streak, close the zipper. Then, large notochordal wave.
Then, you imagine an embryo lying in front of you, head towards the hands. Formation of the neural groove. The neural tube closes. And the neural tube closes. And the neural tube closes. And the neural tube closes. And the neural tube closes.
And gradual establishment of the motility of the growing brain.
Brain expansion.
Cephalic flexion.
Followed by cervical flexion. And the establishment, here, of the pons.
Telencephalization phase.
Occiputs and temporals in the hands.
The hands. Heart development movement. From the primitive streak, you bring your hands down to the coccyx.
You join your hands forward, above the head. Fusion of the two tubes.
And looping of the heart.
Descent of the right hand in rotation to the left.
Heart development movement.
Diaphragm development movement.
And the shoots will form the diaphragmatic pillars here.
Formation of the embryonic delimitation. Formation of zone B, the amniotic sac, the entire amniotic cavity. We start behind the back. It's as if we were extending a large balloon of beautiful honeycomb forward. We were here.
And the meeting of the vitelline vesicle and the amniotic cavity. And the embryonic pedicle will form the umbilical cord. Then, we raise our hands to the level of the angle of Louis. We will make a small turn of the hand. We will make a small turn of the hand. Then, we raise our hands to the level of the angle of Louis.
And establishment of lung formation.
Opening, inspiration.
We raise our hands upwards.
And formation of kidney movement.
We descend. Concentration. Take forehead, kiss forehead, meta is forehead.
Relationship between the kidneys and the descent of the sacrum.
Developmental movement of the sub-diaphragmatic space.
You hold a balloon on the left side.
And you roll the balloon to form the space.
And hepato-gastro-pancreatico-lineal.
Then, rotation of the intestine.
The right hand passes over the left hand. It's as if you were turning counter-clockwise.
The intestine forms with the right hand forming the ascending colon. It's like.
Then, we bring our hands together.
At the level of the posterior parietal peritoneum. We concentrate. We bring our hands towards the midline. We descend towards the pubis.
We go back up to form the uterus or the prostate.
We raise our hands to shoulder level. Developmental movement of the upper and lower limbs. Here, we do the upper limbs.
External rotation.
The thumbs and hands turn to hold a small embryo.
The hands represent this small embryo in formation.
We bring the hands back to the initial position. We take the right thumb with the left hand. We descend to the umbilical level to regain the initial posture. We become aware of this posture. What do we take? We take this posture.
We become aware of finding our axis, the central chain. Vertex, coccyx, sphenobasilar synchondrosis, esophagus, trachea, pericardium,
phrenic center, with the brain's falx, the root of the mesentery, all the way down. We are well-centered and we regain our balance, our equilibrium.